[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the lowest lake on Earth, situated at about 400 meters below sea level on the border between Israel and Jordan.", "correct_answer": "Dead Sea", "incorrect_answers": ["Issyk-Kul", "Balkhash", "Urmia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Shah Rukh Khan, Kajol, Rani Mukherji, and Salman Khan starred together in one of the following famous Bollywood movies.", "correct_answer": "Kuch Kuch Hota Hai", "incorrect_answers": ["Hum Dil De Chuke Sanam", "Dilwale Dulhaniya Le Jayenge", "Dil To Pagal Hai"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What group was popular in the 1960s with the hits Yummy Yummy Yummy and Chewy Chewy?", "correct_answer": "The Ohio Express", "incorrect_answers": ["Velvet Underground", "The Rolling Stones", "The Beatles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of these are not real bodies of water; which one is?", "correct_answer": "North Sea", "incorrect_answers": ["Northwest Sea", "South Sea", "Southeast Sea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the colors of Supermans costume?", "correct_answer": "red, blue, yellow", "incorrect_answers": ["grey, black, blue", "red, purple, yellow", "green, red, blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Blepharoplasty is a cosmetic surgery procedure which aims at improving the appearance of which body part?", "correct_answer": "Eyelids", "incorrect_answers": ["Forehead", "Neck", "Lips"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The hit movie Anchorman was co-written and directed by this former Saturday Night Live writer.", "correct_answer": "Adam McKay", "incorrect_answers": ["Conan OBrien", "Tina Fey", "Tim Herlihy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Whats Love Got to Do With It, what was the name of the song that Ann Marie Bullook sang for Ike Turner at the lounge where they first met?", "correct_answer": "(Darlin) You Know I Love You", "incorrect_answers": ["Down Home Blues", "Hail Mary", "Crazy Blues"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The natural habitat of the Chinchilla is this region in South America.", "correct_answer": "The Andes", "incorrect_answers": ["Tierra del Fuego", "The Atacama Desert", "The Amazon River basin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does the platypus feed its young for the first three to four months?", "correct_answer": "The mother is lactating, but she has no teats.", "incorrect_answers": ["The mother is feeding them with insects.", "The mother is breastfeeding them.", "The young rely on their yolk sacs for food."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In a 1982 movie, Mel Gibson played a post-apocalyptic warrior named Mad Max. In what movie does Mad Max lead a convey driving a fuel-oil semi MACK truck chased by gasoline pirates?", "correct_answer": "The Road Warrior", "incorrect_answers": ["Gone in Sixty Seconds", "Convey", "Thunderdome"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What revelation is made about Pamela, played by Teri Polo, in the 2004 move Meet the Fockers?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["She has a disease.", "She doesnt love Greg.", "She is pregnant."]}]